Bienen, Leigh B.; Papers apap312
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material, 1979-2011, Undated; 2; 7 cubic ft.
  - Homicide Study - Appendix D: Case Summaries [1 of 2], ca. 1985-1988 (Box 1 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 3)
  - Homicide Study - Appendix D: Case Summaries [2 of 2], ca. 1985-1988 (Box 1 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 4)
  - Homicide Study - Coding Interpretations and Instructions, 1985 (Box 1 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 5)
  - Homicide Study - Plea/Trial Code, ca. 1985-1988 (Box 1 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 6)
  - Homicide Study Master List, ca. 1985-1988 (Box 1 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 7)
  - Homicide Study Plea/Trial Code, 1985; Undated (Box 1 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 8)
  - Homicide Study Questionnaire, ca. 1985-1988 (Box 1 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 9)
  - Homicide Study Questionnaire, ca. 1985-1988 (Box 1 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 10)
  - Homicide Study Questionnaire, ca. 1985-1988 (Box 1 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 11)
  - Homicide Study Questionnaire with notes, ca. 1985-1988 (Box 1 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 12)
  - Alfonso and Baur Penalty Phase Training Program (New Jersey), 1986 (Box 1 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 13)
  - Homicide Study Questionnaire and Forms, 1986; Undated (Box 1 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 14)
  - Leigh B. Bienen and Neil Alan Weiner, "The Reimposition of Capital Punishment in New Jersey: Homicide Cases from 1982 - 1986" - Supplement to Preliminary Report, 1987 (Box 1 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 15)
  - Capital Jury Project - William Bones Data, 1987 (Box 1 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 16)
  - Leigh B. Bienen, et. al., "The Reimposition of Capital Punishment in New Jersey: The role of Prosecutorial Discretion" Rutgers Law Review print copy with notes, 1988 (Box 1 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 17)
  - Leigh Bienen, et. al., The Reimposition of Capital Punishment in New Jersey: Interim Report, Part 1 [1 of 2], 1988 (Box 1 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 18)
  - Leigh Bienen, et. al., The Reimposition of Capital Punishment in New Jersey: Interim Report, Part 1 [2 of 2], 1988 (Box 1 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 19)
  - Leigh Bienen, et. al., The Reimposition of Capital Punishment in New Jersey: Interim Report 2 [1 of 3], 1988 (Box 1 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 20)
  - Leigh Bienen, et. al., The Reimposition of Capital Punishment in New Jersey: Interim Report 2 [2 of 3], 1988 (Box 1 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 21)
  - Leigh Bienen, et. al., The Reimposition of Capital Punishment in New Jersey: Interim Report 2 [3 of 3], 1988 (Box 1 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 22)
  - Leigh Bienen, "No Savings In Lives or Money With Death Penalty, 1988 (Box 1 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 23)
  - Leigh Bienen, "No Savings In Lives or Money With Death Penalty," The New York Times, 1988 (Box 1 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 24)
  - Homicide Study - Appendix A,B,C, ca. 1988 (Box 1 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 25)
  - The Special Commission on the Administration of Justice in Cook County - Final Report, 1988 (Box 1 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 26)
  - American Civil Liberties Union of New Jersey and Habeas Corpus, 1989 (Box 1 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 27)
  - Inventory from Watt Espy, Capital Punishment Research Project, 1989 (Box 1 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 28)
  - Manuscripts, notes, research material and correspondence from "Proportionality Review of Capital Cases by State High Courts: Only 'The Appearance of Justice?' " and New York University Talk, 1989-1990 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 1)
  - Capital Jury Project - Natural Science Foundation Grant Proposal, 1990 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 2)
  - Capital Jury Project - Natural Science Foundation proposal to study Capital sentencing, comments by Leigh Bienen, 1990 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 3)
  - Criminologists for Abolition of the Death Penalty, 1990 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 4)
  - Missouri Proportionality review case citations, 1990 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 5)
  - Program - NYU Review of Law and Social Change Colloquium, Challenging the Death Penalty: 1990 and Beyond (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 6)
  - Charles Silagy v. Howard Peters III, 1990 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 7)
  - Statement of David C. Baldus before Committee on the Judiciary, United States House of Representatives concerning Arbitrariness and Discrimination in the Imposition of the Death Penalty, 1990 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 8)
  - Bill Proposing lethal injection, 1991 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 9)
  - Capital Jury Project, National Study of Juror Decision Making in Capital Cases, Grant proposal and Survey Sample, ca. 1991 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 10)
  - Deputy Attorney General Class visit and death penalty legislative hearing transcript, 1991 January 31 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 11)
  - Capital Jury Project - Working Paper 1, Background and Research Design, 1991 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 12)
  - Cost of Capital Punishment - notes, 1991 February 1 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 13)
  - David Margolik, "At the Bar", 1991 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 14)
  - National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty 11th Annual Conference - folder containing notes and materials gathered at conference, 1991 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 15)
  - National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty - Conference follow - ups, 1991 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 16)
  - New Jersey Case Summaries - No Penalty Trial, 1991 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 17)
  - New Jersey Case Summaries - Penalty Trial/Death, 1991 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 18)
  - New Jersey Case Summaries - Penalty Trial/Life, 1991 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 19)
  - Notes on costs of capital punishment, 1991 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 20)
  - Woodrow Wilson School Policy Conference - Leigh Bienen and Douglas Mills: A Decade of Capital Punishment in New Jersey: A Report to the State Legislative, 1991 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 21)
  - WWS Policy Conference on Capital Punishment, 1991 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 22)
  - Appendixes from New Jersey Death Penalty Study, 1992 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 23)
  - Leigh Bienen, Douglas Mills, et. al., A Decade of Capital Punishment in New Jersey - Presented to the New Jersey Assembly Judiciary Committee, 1992 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 24)
  - Leigh B. Bienen and Douglas L. Mills, "Race and County Disparities in Capital Case Processing in New Jersey.", 1992 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 25)
  - Capital Jury Project - National Science Foundation Grant Proposal, 1992 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 26)
  - Capital Jury Project - National Science Foundation Grant Proposal, 1992 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 27)
  - Capital Jury Project - Working Paper 7, "In Their Own Words: How Capital jurors Explain their Life or Death Sentencing Decisions", 1992 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 28)
  - Chicago Prosecutor Misconduct, 1992 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 29)
  - Criteria for Exemption from Human Subjects Review by the Institutional Review Panel (IRP), 1992 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 30)
  - Philadelphia Law and Society Paper - Notes and tables to publish, 1992 May 29 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 31)
  - Herbert I. Weisberg and Xiu Chen, "Can Statistics Reveal when A Death Sentence is Disproportionate?" (Draft), 1992 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 32)
  - Leigh Bienen, "A Good Murder", 1993 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 33)
  - Leigh Bienen, "A Good Murder", 1993 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 34)
  - Capital Jury Project - Bringing in New Jersey, 1993 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 35)
  - Capital Jury Project - denial of permission to interview jurors, 1993 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 36)
  - Capital Jury Project - Interview's Guide, ca. 1993 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 37)
  - Capital Jury Project - Juror Interview Instrument, ca. 1993 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 38)
  - Connecticut v. Michael Ross, 1993 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 39)
  - Flyer - The Jury Project, ca. 1993 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 40)
  - New Jersey Death Penalty Trials Sorted by County/Sentence Date, ca. 1993 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 41)
  - The New Jersey Jury Project: National Study of Juror Decision Making in Capital Cases - Juror Interview Instrument, 1993 (Box 2 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 42)
  - Testimony of Leigh B. Bienen Before the Joint Subcommittee of the Supreme Court Committee on Criminal Practice and Rules of Evidence, 1993 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 1)
  - Untitled Manuscript draft with notes and annotations [may be early draft of Leigh Bienen, "The Proportionality Review of Capital Cases by State High Courts After Gregg: Only The Appearance of Justice", ca. 1993-1995 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 2)
  - Book Review Manuscript, ca. 1999 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 3)
  - Book Review - Manuscript and Correspondence, 1999 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 4)
  - Conference Materials - Homicide Research Working Group Workshop, 1994; 1997 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 5)
  - Jury Survey, Matt, 1994 Fall (Floppy-disk 1)
  - The New Jersey Jury Project - Juror Interview Instrument, 1994 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 6)
  - United States v. Salvatore Lombardino - Government's Memorandum in Support of it's motion for an Anonymous Jury, 1999 September 15 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 7)
  - "A Compilation and Comparison of Statistics concerning Application of the 1977 Illinois Death Penalty", 1995 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 8)
  - James R. Acker and Charles S. Lanier, "Statutory Measures for More Effective Appellate Review of Capital Cases" with notes, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 9)
  - David Baldus, James R. Acker, Leigh Bienen, et. al., Comments on Proposed Uniform Rules for Capital Case Reports and Proposed Capital Case Data Report form, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 10)
  - Elected Judiciary - Encyclopedia of the American Constitution, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 11)
  - Former CA Justice discussing influence of retention vote on Justice, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 12)
  - Gallup Poll - death penalty opinion, 1995; 1997 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 13)
  - "Governor Assails U.S. Delays of Death Cases," Comment re: political pressure on Judges to sentence to death, cite for only 5909 all federal habeas, 1995; 2000 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 14)
  - Material from Jim Acker on Legislative History of New York Death Penalty, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 15)
  - Douglas Mills, David Weisburd, New Jersey v. Joseph Harris, Logical Regression, and New Jersey v. Donald Loftin, with notes, 1995; 1996 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 16)
  - Notes and Annotation on uniform Rules For Capital Case Data Reports, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 17)
  - Prospective Appointments, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 18)
  - Research Table of State death Penalty decision and legislation dates, ca. 1995 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 19)
  - Syllabus - "Persuasion: The Art of Writing In, For, and about the Law", 1995 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 20)
  - A. Leigh Hicks, "The Constitutional of Imposing the Death Sentence on a Non-slayer Participant", ca. 1996 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 21)
  - Appendix A: Preparing a Factual Basis for the Systematic Examination of Racial and Geographical Disparities: The Court's Responsibility, 1996 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 22)
  - Death Row Statistics, 1996 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 23)
  - Intimate Partner Homicide in Chicago over 29 Years, 1996 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 24)
  - Mental Health Preference Declaration, 1996 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 25)
  - Douglas Mills and New Jersey v. Joseph Harris, 1996 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 26)
  - Douglas Mills and New Jersey v. Donald Loftin, 1996; 1997 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 27)
  - Pennsylvania Supreme Court Reversals in Capital Cases, 1996 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 28)
  - Capital Jury Project - William J. Bowers and Benjamin D. Steinen, "Death by False Choice and Forced Choice: Empirical Evidence of Misguided Discretion in Capital Sentencing", (Draft), 1997 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 29)
  - Philosophy and Public Affairs copy center request form, 1997 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 30)
  - List of Illinois Supreme Court opinions in Death Penalty Cases, 1979-1997, ca. 1997 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 31)
  - Leigh B. Bienen, "The Quality of Justice in Capital Cases: Illinois as a Case Study", 1998 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 32)
  - Leigh B. Bienen, "The Quality of Justice in Capital Cases: Illinois as a Case Study", 1998 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 33)
  - "Federal Death Penalty Cases: Recommendations Concerning the Cost and Quality of Defense Representation", 1998 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 34)
  - Illinois State Archives, Chicago Historical Society, and notes of other historical records repository on Chicago Tribune article, 1998 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 35)
  - Horace Kelly case on competency to be executed, ca. 1998 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 36)
  - Pennsylvania v. Mumia Abu - Jamal, 1998 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 37)
  - Prosecuting Judges, 1998 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 38)
  - Public Confidence in Criminal Justice System, 1998 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 39)
  - Questions for Homicide Class, 1998 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 40)
  - State Death Penalty Cases Filed in the United States Court of Appeals for the Seventh Circuit, 1989-1998 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 41)
  - Teaching Criminal Law & Procedure: the Mentally Disabled Defendant, 1998 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 42)
  - Chicago Prosecutor Misconduct, 1999 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 43)
  - Findings and Recommendations of the Special Supreme Court Committee on Capital Cases (Illinois), 1999 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 44)
  - Illinois v. Anthony Porter, 1999 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 45)
  - Publication Correspondence - "The Quality of Justice in Capital Cases: The Illinois Experience", 1999 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 46)
  - George W. Bush and Death Penalty, 2000 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 47)
  - Illinois Appellate Court Judge Morton Zwick political donations, 2000 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 48)
  - Illinois Budget Appropriations Legislation for State Defense and Prosecution, 2000 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 49)
  - Illinois Capital Crime Litigation Act legislation with annotations, 2000 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 50)
  - "Leigh's Law: Searching for Patterns in Chicago Crime", 2000 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 51)
  - Renata Strok, et. al., "Neuropsychological Characteristics of Death Row Inmates", 2000 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 52)
  - Capital punishment data, Fiscal Impact Report of Illinois House Bill and two Articles on costs of Death Penalty, 2001; 2006; 2009 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 53)
  - Illinois Supreme Court Capital Punishment Rules, 2001 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 54)
  - Lethal Injection - Physician Participation, 2001 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 55)
  - David Smith v. Illinois - On Petition for Writ of Certiorari to the Supreme Court of Illinois, 2001 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 56)
  - "Nothing Short of Justice", 2002 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 57)
  - Glenn L. Pierce and Michael L. Radelet, "Race, Region, and Death Sentencing in Illinois, 1988-1997", 2002 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 58)
  - Report of the Governor's Commission on Capital Punishment [1 of 4], 2002 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 59)
  - Report of the Governor's Commission on Capital Punishment [2 of 4], 2002 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 60)
  - Report of the Governor's Commission on Capital Punishment [3 of 4], 2002 (Box 3 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 61)
  - Report of the Governor's Commission on Capital Punishment [4 of 4], 2002 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 1)
  - Thomas P. Sullivan articles on Illinois Governor's Commission on Capital Punishment, 2002 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 2)
  - Thomas P. Sullivan, Comments on the Illinois State's Attorney's Association Response to the Report of the Governor's Commission on Capital Punishment, 2002 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 3)
  - Thomas P. Sullivan, "Repair or Repeal - Report of the Governor's Commission on Capital Punishment", 2002 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 4)
  - Illinois State Budget and Capital Litigation Trust Fund, 2003 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 5)
  - Charles Johnson, "A Bootcamp for Creative Writing ", 2003 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 6)
  - Letter from Governor Rod R. Blagojevich, 2003 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 7)
  - Office if the State's Attorneys Appellate Prosecutor - Report on the Capital Litigation Trust Fund, 2003 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 8)
  - Persuasion Assignment - naked documents, 2003 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 9)
  - Seminar Task Force Report: murder and it's consequences, Fall 2002 - "The Status of the Death Penalty in Illinois as of January 13, 2003", Northwestern University School of Law (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 10)
  - Capital Litigation Trust Fund, 2004; Undated (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 11)
  - John Cullerton, Kirk Dillard, and Peter G. Baroni, "Capital Punishment in Illinois - A model for the Nation" - Internet Printout, 2004 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 12)
  - John Cullerton, Kirk Dillard, and Peter G. Baroni, "Capital Punishment Reform in Illinois: A model for the Nation", 2004 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 13)
  - Illinois House Bill 0576 - Police Training Act, ca. 2004 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 14)
  - Molly Treadway Johnson and Laural L. Hopper, Resource Guide for Managing Capital Cases: Volume I, Federal Death Penalty Trials, 2004 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 15)
  - Lafonso Rollins - footnote for procedures to get wrongful conviction claim, 2004 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 16)
  - Thomas P. Sullivan, "Capital punishment Reform - What's Been Done and what Remains to be Done", 2004 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 17)
  - Thomas P. Sullivan, "Preventing Wrongful Convictions: A Current Report from Illinois", 2004 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 18)
  - Rob Warden, "Illinois Death Penalty Reform: How it Happened, what it Promises", with annotations, 2005 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 19)
  - Rob Warden, "Illinois Death Penalty Reform: How it Happened, what it Promises", 2005 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 20)
  - Rob Warden, "Illinois Death Penalty Reform: How it Happened, what it Promises", 2005 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 21)
  - "Death Penalty Decision Guidelines", prepared by the office of the Illinois Attorney General and the Illinois State's Attorney Association, 2006 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 22)